http://www.inflowinventory.com/privacy

Privacy policy(Handling of Personal Information)CONSENTBY USING OUR SERVICES, YOU CONSENT TO (i) THE COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION, (ii) THE INSTALLATION ON YOUR DEVICES BY US OR THIRD PARTIES OF THE SOFTWARE AND/OR COOKIES NOTED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE/USER AGREEMENTS, AND (iii) RECEIVING EMAIL AND OTHER COMMUNICATIONS, BY/FROM ARCHON SYSTEMS INC. AND POSSIBLY THIRD PARTIES, IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, WHICH MAY BE CHANGED FROM TIME TO TIME. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS, DO NOT USE OUR SERVICES.IF WE DECIDE TO CHANGE OUR PRIVACY POLICY, WE WILL POST THOSE CHANGES ON THIS PAGE SO THAT YOU ARE AWARE OF WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT, HOW WE USE IT AND UNDER WHAT CIRCUMSTANCES WE DISCLOSE IT.NOTWITHSTANDING THE OTHER PROVISIONS OF THIS POLICY, (i) ARCHON SYSTEMS INC. RESERVES THE RIGHT TO DISCLOSE ALL INFORMATION, INCLUDING PERSONAL INFORMATION, TO REGULATORY AUTHORITIES, LAW ENFORCEMENT AGENCIES OR AS REQUIRED BY APPLICABLE LAW, AND (ii) ARCHON SYSTEMS INC. MAY ALSO USE YOUR INFORMATION, INCLUDING PERSONAL INFORMATION, AS PERMITTED BY LAW TO ENFORCE OUR RIGHTS AND TO PROTECT: OUR RIGHTS OR PROPERTY, OUR WEBSITES, OR OUR USERS AND OTHER CLIENTS.Your ObligationsYour use of our services is subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use/User Agreement, or other agreement, and related policies and guidelines applicable to the service. In this regard You are required to respect the privacy and property rights of the other users of our services and Archon, and failure to do so may result in us suspending or terminating Your use of our products and services in our sole discretion.TransparencyBecause Archon Systems Inc. (“Archon”, “we”, “us” and/or “our”) gather certain types of information about our users (“users”, “You” and “Your”), we feel You should understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This Privacy Policy discloses what personal information we gather and how we use it.GeneralPlease note that “including”, the phrases “e.g.,” or “for example” and any derivatives of any of the foregoing mean “including, without limitation”; and the examples provided should not be considered to be all-inclusive or limiting.Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the products and services offered by Archon.Our Privacy Policy does not apply to products or services offered by, or the information practices of, other enterprises or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed or offered to You in the use of our products, services and websites, or other websites linked to our services and websites (e.g. Shopify, Dymo, Quickbooks). You should theretofore review their policies to understand their practices before you link to, or transact business with, them through our services. We are not responsible or liable for such parties’ use of Your information.Accessibility of Your Information – How You Control ItOur services, and in particular the Online Showroom feature of our inFlow Cloud™ Services, are designed so that users publish their product information online for their customers or public to see. Our services do not filter or monitor in respect of this.You have control over, and You are responsible for, what information is accessible to other users of InFlow Cloud™ and the public. This is done via Your choices in the Online Showroom Settings of our services, and by specific actions that You take from time to time when using our services such as invoicing or adding users to Your account.Be careful: Your use of our services can also result in making other information accessible to others which is not covered by the Online Showroom Settings as a result of actions that You take. For example, if You choose to allow Public Access to Your Online Showroom and choose to show the Pricing Information, then anyone on the Internet will be able to see Your products with their respective prices. When You add a user to Your account or You issue an invoice through our services, You are handling personal information and should ensure that You do so in compliance with applicable laws and regulations.Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other registered users of our products or services and their respective companies and organizations. Our products and services also enable you to exchange data with third party services, such as Shopify. You should review the data/information policies of other users and third party services before transacting business with them or interacting with them.Please note that we reserve the right to change the Online Showroom Settings and their related default behavior within our services, but we will post notice of such changes on our affected website(s).Information that We Gather and TrackWe gather all information that our users input in the course of registering to use our products and services. We maintain records of Your contact with us, including customer support interactions. This includes all information that is required to register to use and pay for our services, and all optional, voluntary submissions that You input into our websites and into our services.We do not store payment information directly, we use a third-party payment provider called Stripe which stores the information You provide regarding payment. Our agreement with them requires that they use that information only for the purposes of processing your payment(s) to us. The personal information that You provide that is retained and used by us in the course of these activities consists of:NameEmailPhone NumberFor payment purposes Stripe also obtains:Credit Card numberName on CardBilling AddressTracking: We also gather information, including personal information, derived from Your use of our services and visits to our website(s) using third party products (Google Analytics, Drip, Webinar Jam, Calendly, Get Feedback). This includes log data, Your IP address and similar information that is generated when You use our services and/or our software programs, and includes from where and when You log into our services, what devices You use to access our services, when You enter or leave our website(s), where You go on our website(s) what aspects of our services You use, who You interact with within our user community, e-mails and e-mail logs, live chat logs, and passwords. This information can be, and is, linked by us to the individual user.CookiesWe place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of Your computer or other device. The cookie itself does not contain personal information, although it will enable us to relate Your use of our website(s) and services to personal information that You have specifically and knowingly provided. We use cookies to track user patterns and preferences (as described above: Information that We Gather and Track – Tracking).In addition the third party services that we use for Tracking (Google Analytics, Drip, Webinar Jam, Calendly, Get Feedback) may place cookies on Your device so that we and they can understand what You are interested in. The techniques such third parties’ use to gather IP addresses, cookie identifiers, website activity and other information is set out at their websites.You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If You have set your browser to warn You before accepting cookies, You will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to view the public parts of our website(s), however You do need cookies to use our services.Further, please note that cookies can track all activity that occurs after they are placed in your system. Regular “clearing” of cookies from Your systems may assist in maintaining Your privacy.Our Use of the InformationAccess to personal information and Your data is restricted to Archon employees and consultants which require access to perform their jobs.We do not sell Your personal information to third parties.We use the personal information that You provide to us and that we gather to provide our services, including billing and support.The information that we gather in the course of tracking Your use of our services and visits to our website(s) is used by us to improve our products and services.Unless we have received explicit consent from an individual user to divulge his or her personal information to a third party, we do not disclose personal information about an individual user except to carry out his/her instructions or as reasonably necessary to provide the services that she/he has registered for, or as noted in this Privacy Policy.However, information we collect from You may be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale, acquisition, merger, financing, insolvency or bankruptcy involving us.In addition Your personal information is accessible to our suppliers providing us with goods and services related to providing You our services (e.g. our cloud service provider Microsoft Azure, and we use Zendesk, UserVoice, Aircall, and Setmore products for customer support).We also use Your contact information to send out notices and information about our products and services, including third party notices relating to our services. You can opt out of receiving these communications by going to the unsubscribe link embedded in the communication and following the procedure described there.Protection of the InformationWe have implemented commercially available security measures to secure Your data and personal information, and we use reputable cloud service providers (Microsoft Azure) to provide the data storage related to our services. Security measures include:Secured and encrypted version of the HTTP transportation protocolAnonymizing of passwordsIP-based firewall whitelist for all direct database accessStoring of each user’s data in its own individual siloHowever because our services utilize the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any information You submit to us will be free from unauthorized intrusion that could result in in being accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. We also cannot guarantee that other technical issues, including software coding errors, may not result in an inadvertent disclosure, alteration or destruction of Your information.You control your own password, and should ensure that it is secure and strong. Also remember that Your communications with us and other users using e-mail, IM and similar means are not encrypted, and thus potentially vulnerable. Please ensure that You have appropriate back up for all Your information.As a result, we shall not be responsible or liable for any loss of privacy, disclosure of information, harm, damage or loss that may result from unauthorized access to or disclosure of any information that You have provided to us or transmitted through or to our services. Please also refer to our Terms and Conditions of Use/User Agreement for the service You are using regarding further limitations in respect of our liability.If Archon does become aware of any unlawful access or misuse of a Your personal information stored on equipment or in facilities controlled or managed by it, or unauthorized access to such equipment or facilities resulting in disclosure of personal data, we will promptly (i) notify the affected users of the incident; (ii) investigate the incident and provide the affected users with detailed information about it; and (iii) take prompt steps to remedy the vulnerability, if any, that led to the incident.Data Retention and RemovalWe retain the personal information that You provide and the information we collect in connection with our websites and our services for five years after you cease to use our services or products. However if You notify us in accordance with our applicable Terms and Conditions of Use/User Agreement that you no longer want to use a service, or we terminate Your use of our service(s), we will deactivate your profile and related information so that it is no longer readily available to others or to You.Within a reasonable period of time after a termination, we will not use Your personal information except as reasonably necessary for us to enforce this Privacy Policy and/or our Terms and Conditions of Use/User Agreement, to comply with obligations imposed upon us by law or regulation, or to resolve any disputes between You and others. We will, however, continue to use the aggregated tracking information derived from Your use of our services and visits to our website(s) for the purposes described above in this Privacy Policy.You can contact us at any time to ask us to remove Your personal information from our systems, and we will do so through an irreversible anonymization that will also result in the termination of our services if any were still active. Please note too that this only affects the personal information in our systems or that of our suppliers that we control, and will not result in the removal of Your personal information that You have made available to others using our products or services that may have been retained outside of our systems or those of our suppliers.Accessing, Updating or Correcting Your DataUnless Your use of our services or products has terminated or been suspended, You are able to view and update most of the Your information, including all of Your personal information, through Your account(s). If You are having trouble updating your personal information yourself, please contact us to request the removal of inaccurate or incorrect information and personal information in Your account(s); and Archon will respond to such requests within 30 days.If you have such a request, or you have any questions about this policy or Your personal information that we maintain, please contact us as follows:Our contact pageorBy Mail or Courier Archon Systems Inc. 260 Carlaw Avenue, Unit 207, Toronto Ontario, M4M 3L1 Attention: Privacy MattersModification to this Privacy PolicyArchon may modify this Privacy Policy at any time in its sole discretion. If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will post notice of such change on our website(s) and we may contact You at the email(s) You have provided us.If the change(s) we make has the effect of introducing a use of Your personal information that is inconsistent with the immediately previous version of this policy, this will be specifically set out in the notice.If any modification or change is unacceptable to You, You agree that Your only recourse is to terminate Your use of our service(s).Your continued use of a service following our posting of a change and/or a modified or new privacy policy on our website(s) will constitute Your binding acceptance of same and You agree that all use by You will be subject to the terms and conditions of the modified or new Privacy Policy, which shall apply until we post a modified or new Privacy Policy.Updated May 2018. ProductPricing Hardware Download Release notesCompanyAbout usPartner programRefer inFlowFeaturesAll features Manage inventory Barcoding Manufacturing Selling & invoicing B2B portal Purchasing & receiving Reporting Integrations & API MobileUse CasesWarehouse Assembly Wholesale Asset tracking Field service United States Canada United Kingdom Australia United Arab Emirates WorldwideSupportKnowledge baseContact supportVideos FB community Blog Webinars Cloud statusGet started — it’s freeNo credit card required. Sign up now!      © 2020 inFlow Inventory Software. Archon Systems Inc. All rights reserved.Sitemap Privacy PolicypartnerStackReferralStart your free 14 day trialAlready have an account? Log inEmailFirst namePhone numberPassword I agree to the terms and conditions of useCheck your emailWe sent an email to [EMAIL@DOMAIN.COM]. Inside you'll find a link you need to click to verify your email. This lets us verify it's really you who's requesting the free trial!If you didn't get the email, we can send it again. Try again.Remember to check your junk mail and add support@inflowinventory.com to your contact list.
